in a little bit deeper to think about some of those growth drivers a key element of our story
is driving depth in the existing sites and expansion into urology that continues and I think
we're making good progress on that front
and then we also expect the hormone sensitive approvals in the second half there we expect the
hormone sensitive indication to increase the total patient pool available to PluVicto by 75 percent so
a substantial expansion and one that I think will enable us to get the next inflection of growth for
PluVicto you can see here at the bottom of the slide some of the data on the number of sites
so again we were a bit nervous about this we were already a few weeks away at the bottom of the slide
and here it is over from the beginning and there we are we've moved on to the next stage in the
administration of the national health manifolds and that's the post-diagnosis data unit in the
second half of the slide and then we got a big shift up to the right side and the first two
days we had two different diets uh and those were the pre-diagnosis the first two were a
type 1 and pre-diagnosis and that was based on the other two diets and that was the pre-diagnosis
and the second one we got was the pre-diagnosis uh and so that was the pre-diagnosis of that diet
and the point is that we've been able to make RLT standards that's available now broadly in the communities
31% growth in the quarter. We continue to outpace the advanced lipid lowering market. But I think in
the U.S., the next inflection point we would expect is when we get the outcomes data in the
first part of next year in the secondary prevention setting. And that'll be an important milestone for
us. Now, when you think about some of the other data, the highlights we're seeing, we're seeing
that we are expanding in the Medicare Part B population up 11 points versus prior year. That's
about two-thirds of our current business. And we also see that our TRXs are consistently up 41%
for prior year. So I think all heading in the right direction, consistent, steady growth across
the U.S. in the buy and build segment. Outside of the U.S., 106% constant currency growth. That
was led by China. The NRDL listing unlocked significant demand. It is early days, so I
think we'll have to see how the coming quarters evolve in China to really understand how much of
this was a bolus versus not.
This is a steady demand, but I think the early benchmarks that we're looking at suggest very
strong demand in China and something that we're excited about for our future SIRNA portfolio.
Now, lastly, in terms of evidence base for Lectio, I mentioned the importance of the
outcomes trials, but we also are advancing toward, we received an FDA approval for adolescents